Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Small Accessions, 1895-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Inventory of Small Accessions, 1895-2006 and undated
  - Accession Unidentified Accessions
    - Information Center, competitive advertising files, 1997 (Box 34)
    - International Managers List, Past and Present, 1985-1986 (Box 34)
    - JWT Fund Blue Book, 1989 (Box 34)
    - JWT history, 1928 (Box 34)
    - JWT Management Leadership Program at Duke, 1995 (Box 34)
    - JWT publication: Directors and Boards, 1993 (Box 34)
    - JWT publication: Live Wire (mature market focus), 2002 (Box 34)
    - JWT publication: Once Over Lightly (New York Office), 1986 (Box 34)
    - JWT self-promotion stamp, circa 1900s (Box 34)
    - Letter from Mr. Thompson to O. S. Marden concerning his book Peace Power and Plenty (copy of book included), 1910 (Box 34)
    - NOAB Bureaugram (article by Norman Strouse), 1948 (Box 34)
    - Novell print advertisements, 2003 (Box 34)
    - Rinso case history 1931-1937, circa 1938 (Box 34)
    - Business Kinetics kit (New Business), undated (Box 35)
    - JWT Paris show reel. 2001. Umatic NTSC. 11:00. (Box 36)
    - Scala Thompson (Bucharest, Romania) show reel. 2001. VHS PAL. 10:30. (Box 36)
    - Scala Thompson (Bucharest, Romania) special events. 2001. VHS PAL. 11:00. (Box 36)
    - North America reel. 1992. VHS. (Box 36)
    - Honor Spingarn Tranum reminiscence of Helen Lansdowne Resor (Aunt Nell). 2001. Audiocassette. (Box 36)
    - JWT New York show reel. 2006. DVD. (Box 36)
  - Accession: Restricted Materials
    - Corporate policy, 1995-2001 (Box 37)
    - Directory, 2003 (Box 37)
    - Worldwide Offices Address Book, 2005 (Box 37)
    - The Lab (JWT Interactive launch), 1999 (Box 37)